THE CHARACTERS, INSTITUTIONS
COMPANIES, AND PLACES
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTIONAL
The child
your father saved.
That was me.
What
are you talking about?
In the apartment I lived in,
there was a big fire.
The door to my room was blocked,
so I couldn't escape.
Someone came to save me.
Before the building collapsed,
he handed me over to the firefighters…
He saved my life.
So I had been searching for his family.
I recently found out his name.
Mr. Kang Kyung-tae.
Are you sure?
Did you really verify it?
It doesn't make sense.
How could you…
How…
That's impossible.
I need some time alone.
You should go.
Why is it you of all people?
Why?
I resented my dad so much.
I hated him so much.
I wish
you hadn't told me.
You should've kept me in the dark.
How will I…
I…
How am I supposed to
look at you from now on?
I will wait
until you had enough time to think.
I WILL WAIT UNTIL YOU HAD
ENOUGH TIME TO THINK.
Why are you wearing sunglasses
all of a sudden?
Did you get a stye?
The sun is strong today.
What? It's awfully cloudy.
Eun-ho.
Eun-ho?
Can I have a minute with you?
Okay.
A month?
I knew you wouldn't be worried about it.
You've been too busy dating
that you lost track of time.
We agreed on six months at the beginning.
So you have a little more than a month.
You might need
some time to think about it.
That's why I brought it up early.
I see. Thank you.
We also agreed that
you could look for another job.
Don't hesitate to let me know
if you want to change jobs.
Of course,
I'd love to make you stay
and keep working with you.
That's only what I want.
Discuss it with Ji-yun before deciding.
Okay.
I'll think about it and let you know.
Gosh.
Ji-yun might not want
to stay away from you.
She might keep you working here.
Let me know when you're ready.
This is Jang Seo-young
with a background in law.
After working at Seoul
Central District Prosecutors' Office,
she was on the legal team
at Haeseon Electronics.
Currently, she's the CEO at an IT company.
She's known for her expertise
in risk management.
The last candidate is Oh Min-seok.
After studying law,
he was certified as a lawyer
at Herald Law School.
After working in mergers and acquisitions
at a major law firm in Korea,
he became the youngest CEO
at a game company three years ago.
All of them
fit the requirements we wanted.
Let's meet them individually.
Mr. Yu, please arrange the meetings.
Yes, ma'am.
Meeting's over.
Good job, everyone.
KANG JI-YUN, CEO
Jeong-nam.
Oh, Mr. Kim!
Over here.
You got much younger than before.
From afar, I thought
you were a college student.
That must be why
people were staring at me.
- Sit down.
- Please have a seat.
- You grilled the meat so well.
- Thank you.
How have you been?
When you left the company like that,
I felt terrible.
Actually,
I'm in a different field now.
It wasn't the right fit for me.
I'm being trained at a small company
someone referred me to.
Really?
Where you work isn't important.
What matters is that you're working.
Have a drink.
- Let me serve you first.
- Okay.
It's been so long.
Thank you for your time.
I'm the one who's thankful.
- Let me pour you one.
- Okay.
How about you?
Are you still busy these days?
I read that Peoplez is in charge
of finding a CEO for NEXT.
Well, yes.
Things are still going well at Peoplez.
Have you started searching for candidates?
We wouldn't be Peoplez
if we were still searching.
- We started contacting our candidates.
- Already?
Yeah.
Ms. Kang works insanely fast.
She isn't just fast.
She's one step ahead of anyone else.
- It's surprising.
- Really?
Even this time,
instead of those formerly in management,
people like lawyers and journalists
Such candidates…
No, I can't. It's a trade secret.
A trade secret?
Sure, that's important!
Hello, Ms. Kim.
Peoplez is contacting those
with a legal or journalist background
instead of managers.
- Are you sure this time?
- Yes, I'm sure.
I heard it directly
from a Peoplez employee.
From Peoplez's database that you have,
bring me a list of lawyers and journalists
that Kang Ji-yun would contact.
Don't forget that this is
your last chance.
I would be so scared to be your enemy.
You must dislike Ms. Kang so much
for you to attack her
from all directions.
I mean, is what we're doing not enough?
If I'm taking it away from her,
I shouldn't leave her a single crumb.
Is everything going smoothly?
Of course.
There can't be any problem.
A lot of money is at stake.
Please come in.
Hello, I'm from Ikonic Biotechnology.
I'm CEO Park Young-min.
- Nice to meet you. I'm Kang Ji-yun.
- Yes.
- Please have a seat.
- Okay.
Wow, I like your office.
You're impressive.
Everyone talked about Peoplez
when they recommended me search firms.
I heard that you're also in charge
of finding a CEO for NEXT.
Rumors spread fast.
You must be busy,
but please help us out too.
We're nowhere near NEXT,
but many want to invest in us
for our technology development.
Things are going well for us now.
We worked hard for several years
after getting our new drug patented.
It's finally happening.
I heard that you'll sign a contract
with a German pharmaceutical company.
Yes, since then,
we've been getting investment offers.
We've been very busy.
Our investment consultant told us
that stabilizing the company is important
at a time like this.
Before our new drug gets commercialized,
we plan to focus on development.
Please recommend us competent researchers.
Sure.
Why aren't you going in?
Oh, go ahead.
What? Are you alone?
Yes, why?
Eun-ho left without going in.
Oh, really?
You two are so careful.
In case people get suspicious from
seeing you together in the break room?
Have you discussed about his contract?
What did you decide?
- Contract?
- Yes. Didn't he bring it up?
His contract period is almost over,
so I told him to discuss it with you.
Oh, is it up already?
Did you fight or something?
Is something wrong?
Mi-ae.
How about some soju with me?
How could he
be Eun-ho, of all people?
Is this meant to be
or an ill-fated relationship?
Isn't my dad nasty?
What he's done to me was enough.
I was trying to live without being lonely.
It's about him all over again.
So what are you going to do?
Stay with him.
What's the problem with staying with him?
To be brutally honest, it isn't
Eun-ho's fault that your dad died.
Aren't you glad that
your dad saved Eun-ho?
I've been resenting Dad all my life.
I still can't understand his choice.
Stop resenting him.
Stop hating him.
Seo Mi-ae, how could she?
When you told me…
there were two people
who brought you where you are now,
is one of them
my dad?
He told me not to give up
and survive no matter what.
What your father told me that day
has stayed with me, even now.
Whenever I feel like collapsing,
I think of his voice and endure.
So that's why I'm here
as well as Byeol.
All thanks to him.
Ji-yun.
You're number one in my life.
Not this one.
Not this one either.
Byeol, which outfit are you looking for?
What you're wearing is pretty too.
No, this isn't good enough.
What do you mean?
You look like a princess to me.
Princesses don't dress like this.
Byeol, clothes aren't important.
You're so beautiful.
Let's just go in this outfit.
We're both late.
You only care about work.
- What?
- You have no idea.
I hate you!
But…
Byeol.
Seol, I love your outfit today.
You look like a princess.
Thanks.
Byeol.
Is that how you're dressed today?
You don't look like a princess.
Aren't you going to the party today?
Ji-young is having
her birthday party today.
It's a princess party.
I know.
Are you going?
- No, I'm not going.
- Why not?
All the girls are going.
That sounds boring.
I'm going to go read at Uncle's bookstore.
I see.
- Kang-seok.
- Hey, Ji-yun.
Sis!
Hi, Byeol.
She must be excited to see you at least.
I don't know what happened,
but she's feeling down today.
It's not what you think.
Is that why you've been sighing
without reading your favorite books?
What's wrong? Did something bad happen?
Let's talk over there.
What? Are you keeping it a secret from me?
You're a man, so you won't understand.
Gosh, that's making me feel disappointed.
Okay, you girls have a deep conversation.
- Really?
- Yes.
Byeol.
Let's go.
- Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday, dear Ji-young…
Byeol…
Sorry for being late.
Happy birthday, Ji-young.
Oh, thanks.
Who…
Oh, hello.
I'm a close friend of Byeol's.
Shall we give her the gift?
It's so big.
Here's your present.
Thank you for being born, Ji-young.
BABY TWINS TWO-STORY HOUSE
Thank you, Byeol.
Going down!
Sis, thank you so much for today.
You're the best.
There's no need to thank me.
We're friends.
Friends are supposed to help each other.
Feel free to tell me when
something like this happens again.
Can I really?
Dad doesn't understand this stuff.
That's how dads are.
Was your dad like that too?
Yes.
My dad was worse.
He was bad at tying my hair too.
- Really?
- Yes.
He tied my hair so tight
that he pulled out my hair.
He could only tie it up. He didn't know
how to braid my hair like yours.
My dad is really good at tying my hair.
Disco, crisscross, and centipede hair.
He's even good at braiding.
Sis,
can I borrow your phone?
- My phone?
- I want to call my dad.
I think he might be upset.
I told him this morning that I hated him.
I want to say sorry.
Dad!
- Did you eat something delicious?
- Yes.
- Did you have fun?
- Dad.
- Yes?
- I missed you.
- You said you hated me this morning.
That's because I like you that much.
Because you like me?
Sis told me
that you hate them
as much as you like them.
MINT CHOCOLATE MILK
KANG KYUNG-TAE
Dad, I'm here.
It took me a long time
getting here.
Dad.
It's been really difficult for me.
After you passed away,
I didn't know what to do.
I hated you so much.
I thought it would help me live.
I think I wanted to resent someone.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Until now,
I never smiled at you.
I miss you.
I miss you, Dad.
- Hello.
Doors are closing.
Could you hold…
Doors are opening.
Why aren't you getting in?
Doors are closing.
Thank you, Eun-ho.
For growing up…
to be such a good person.
Aren't you going to hold it?
I will never
let go of this hand.
So,
you don't let go either.
Thank you.
Let's go, Ms. Kang.
Let me check. Hello…
Good morning.
There's no turning back now.
Yes.
That's why I did it.
- Mr. Kim.
- Yes?
A bug might get into your mouth.
I never imagined it.
Why? How could they?
Am I the only one who's in shock?
I already knew about it.
Really? I had no idea.
The two of them
were pretty bad at hiding it.
Yes, I'm back in the office.
I'll call you back after looking it up.
Okay.
Gyu-rim,
you should've reported to me first
after seeing that.
- How could you keep it to yourself?
- Should I have spread a rumor?
- Give me your hand.
- No.
- All of a sudden,
- Peoplez is full of love.
- No way.
- It's not the right time.
- I mean…
- No.
- It's okay.
No way.
I said it's okay.
Is there someone else dating at work?
Don't report things like this.
Kyung-hwa, it was a good time
to tell them.
Are you out of your mind?
It's driving me nuts.
May I get closer?
Yes, hold my hand too.
Kids must not feel hot.
Is Seo-jun's mom not here yet?
She must be busy.
His grandma comes more often.
Speaking of Seo-jun,
he doesn't seem to take
after his mom, does he?
Does he take after his dad?
You didn't know?
She isn't Seo-jun's mom by blood.
Really? No wonder…
That's why the child is…
What about him?
What's wrong with Seo-jun?
It just seems like
there's a certain shadow about him.
Shadow, my foot!
There's no child as cheerful as him.
Seo-jun has been loved by his mom
as much as any other kid.
Yes, of course. You're right.
Isn't it your son the one
who called us half a family last time?
What would he learn from a mom like you?
Kids can say such things.
He apologized enough.
There are things that we shouldn't say.
It's a parents' duty to teach their kids.
Are you saying that
I didn't educate my child?
Giving birth doesn't make
someone a good mom.
Do you even know what my daughter
went through to raise Seo-jun?
Compared to you who talks
about others behind their backs,
my daughter is a much better mother.
Ma'am, how could you say--
That's enough.
The children might hear you.
Do you want them to find out?
Mom.
Did you have a bad day today?
Why would I have a bad day?
I'm just thinking of Seo-jun.
If he hears that
he doesn't take after his mom,
how terrible would he feel?
You said that Seo-jun didn't hear them.
He didn't hear them today,
but he could hear them in the future.
Su-hyeon.
Let's tell Seo-jun the truth.
Mom--
Don't let him find out from someone else.
You tell him first.
No matter how much I think about it,
it's for the best.
Either way,
he will find out one day.
Why isn't there a picture book today?
Aren't you going to read?
Instead of reading a book,
I have something to tell you today.
A story?
What is it?
Seo-jun, I had
one sister.
She was amazing, pretty, and kind.
She was a cheerful person.
She married a wonderful person,
and even had a beautiful baby.
Where is she now?
She's in heaven,
where only good people go.
From there,
she's watching over us.
The two of them left me a present
so that I wouldn't be lonely.
That present was you.
I have a video.
Do you want to watch it?
Okay.
He's so adorable.
- Is that me?
- He's so cute.
He's so beautiful.
- He's so tiny.
- Yes, and
- this is your mom and dad.
- Come and join us.
- Say hello to your aunt.
- Okay.
Aunt.
- Hello, Seo-jun.
- How cute.
Welcome to our family.
- Welcome.
- Seo-jun.
- What's that?
- He's going to grow a lot.
- Is it tasty?
He can even stand up.
Good job.
- Walk, walk.
- Do you want to go there?
Walk, walk.
Let's go to your dad.
- Go to your dad.
- Here.
Good boy!
How adorable.
It's been a long time
since I saw you as a baby.
What do you think?
Don't the three of you look similar?
Yeah.
Seo-jun.
Your mom and dad
loved you very much.
By the way,
why did Mom and Dad go to heaven?
There was an accident.
Your parents got hurt a lot.
They went somewhere
where they won't be hurt anymore.
- Mom.
- Yes?
Does it mean that I have two moms?
Right.
You have two moms.
You also have a dad.
They may not be with you,
but if you remember them,
they'll be with you.
Okay.
Mom.
Thank you for raising me.
Seo-jun.
I love you very much.
I love you too, Mom.
Why are you still at work?
Hey.
Why didn't you go home?
Is something wrong?
I don't come here
only when something's wrong.
I had a meeting nearby,
and I thought of you.
Is everything really okay?
Are things okay with Chairman Woo?
Of course, same as always.
He still doesn't like me.
Got a lot to do?
A lot happened during the day.
I needed some time to think.
What is it about?
It's Rainbow Bingsu.
It's Ms. Jung's book.
It's by Seo-jun's mother.
Wait, do you know Seo-jun's mother?
Oh, well…
I've met her a few times.
Why?
Did something happen to Seo-jun?
She must have a lot on her mind.
WRITER JUNG SU-HYEON
What are you doing right now?
What?
Are you okay?
You came.
I'm sorry for calling you so suddenly.
It's just that
I had no one else to talk to.
How did you know that was my expertise?
Say everything you want to say.
I'm a good listener.
I'm a pro-listener, you know?
I miss my sister.
I just miss my sister a lot today.
Su-jin.
Am I doing a good job?
Didn't you just hear it?
She said you're doing very well.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to make you cry.
Don't be sorry.
It's okay.
HEADHUNTING WORK CONTRACT
I'm sorry for making you wait.
Don't be. I prefer to make it clear.
You accepted my request.
It shows that my company can be trusted.
You must be quite busy.
I saw many articles
about Ikonic Biotechnology.
Yes, it's hard to keep up.
With the sudden increase in size,
I feel anxious and puzzled
at the same time.
You're being rewarded for your
long commitment to develop the new drug.
Speaking of which,
could Peoplez exclusively take charge
of hiring our personnel?
The company will keep getting bigger.
I'm a researcher stuck in the lab all day,
so I'm hopeless in this field.
It's hard to estimate how many more
employees I need to hire.
If Peoplez takes charge
of searching for our future employees,
I'll give you a share in my company.
As you know, the value could grow
exponentially if we go public.
Think of it as growing
with a company with potential.
Please accept my offer.
Thank you for the offer.
I'll think about it.
Sure.
Mr. Kim.
Hey, Mr. Yu.
Is something wrong?
I'm not sure about it,
but I can't get it off my mind.
Changing the direction
- might be okay.
- It's good.
This coffee…
My friend is working at NEXT.
That's why I'm very interested…
Why is Jeong-nam with Sung-woong?
It could work.
- Mr. Kim, what are you doing?
- It's nothing. I'm coming.
Now that we met up, I wanted to ask…
Were Jeong-nam and Sung-woong close?
I'm not sure. Why?
Oh, it's nothing.
Let's go.
He used to work here?
Yes, his name is Go Jeong-nam.
After our project with NEXT became public,
he contacted me and we met up.
Since then, he kept asking questions.
It made me uncomfortable,
so I ignored his calls.
He definitely told me
that he left this field.
If he keeps seeing employees from Peoplez,
he must have an ulterior motive.
- Right?
- Yes.
Did he contact you right after
the article about NEXT got published?
The one who needs information
related to that the most…
Career Way.
Could it be why their candidates
overlapped with ours?
I'll find out.
- Did you say anything else?
- No.
I'm not that stupid.
I read that Peoplez is in charge
of finding a CEO for NEXT.
Instead of those formerly in management,
people like lawyers and journalists…
No, I can't.
It's a trade secret.
Mr. Yu.
I think I made a mistake.
Dong-gi, it's me. Can you do me a favor?
Can you make a request to Career Way?
Like it's from Hansu Electronics.
You're amazing. Thanks.
Ms. Kang, I verified that
Go Jeong-nam works at Career Way.
Does it mean Jeong-nam has been
stealing information on our candidates?
And he approached Mr.
Kim to steal information?
I'm sorry, Ms. Kang.
I know people can't be trusted,
but I didn't expect this.
I treated Jeong-nam so well.
How could he betray me?
Did he take our database
when he left Peoplez?
Ms. Kang, we shouldn't let him
get away with this.
We need to come up with a new plan.
- Jeong-nam.
- Mr. Kim.
I'm sorry for being so late.
It's okay.
- Sit down.
- Okay.
The meeting took longer than I thought.
As it's an important project,
it's not easy to decide on the candidates.
So have the candidates been decided?
Yes, they've been decided.
Mr. Kim, would you like
something cool to drink?
If it's on you.
- I'll buy you a drink.
- Wait.
Before that, I need to go to the restroom.
Actually, I'll take my time.
I was worried about being late to see you,
I didn't have a chance to go.
I'll be right back.
Way to go, Mr. Kim.
Information on our candidates
was handed over to Career Way.
So they think that
it's our final list of candidates?
Serves them right for cheating.
This feels satisfying.
Shall we start discussing
our real list of candidates?
Yes, ma'am.
We'll start searching for candidates
from the beginning today.
"Resignation rate at NEXT?"
People often change jobs and resign
in this field.
While taking that into consideration,
it'd be worthwhile to take a look
at the resignation rate graph.
At NEXT, people with
the highest resignation rate are
managers and senior managers
of five and ten years.
The most important middle tier at NEXT.
The essential workers left the company,
and only old-timers remain?
Yes, centered around a CEO
with a programming background,
there came about a discrimination
against nonprogrammers.
The executives are only interested
in keeping their positions.
Hey,
who do you think will be our new CEO?
Will they do it right this time?
That has nothing to do with it.
I just hope our workplace politics
won't scare him away.
- Do you know who I pity the most?
- Who?
You and me who get ignored
for not being programmers.
But we can't even resign.
Hey, hey.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
When employees are saying that,
it means that things are rotten
at the workplace.
The real crisis at NEXT
may not be external,
but internal.
It might be better to search candidates
from the employees' perspective.
What eventually changes the company
is its employees.
That's all I have.
From now on, we'll be focusing
on NEXT's internal crisis.
We'll start from the beginning
and find the real problem at NEXT
from the employees' perspective.
SEARCHING REVIEWS ON COMPANY
NEXT
"COMPARED TO THE SIZE,
LACK OF SOLIDARITY AT WORK"
"AT NEXT,
ONLY BROWNNOSERS GET PROMOTED"
"PROGRAMMERS
GET SPECIAL TREATMENT"
They lost everyone who's competent.
Talkers.
Only those who know how to talk
remain in high positions.
Darn it.
Could you find me a new job instead?
Cooperation? Ha!
I can't even talk with programmers.
I only do what I get paid for.
Not like I get paid more for working hard.
Won't it be better with a new CEO?
Wouldn't it be great
to get rid of all the old-timers?
Look how naive he is.
Want in on a secret?
A new CEO has already been decided.
Again, it's someone to their liking.
Management at NEXT is so predictable.
Just drink.
If you don't mind me asking,
could you tell me
what you consider
as the most important in management?
That's a hard question.
I don't know if it answers your question,
but on my first day at work,
there's something that I always do.
Ms. Kang,
what do you think of this candidate?
He has enough experience
in human resources.
He doesn't have much field experience.
What about this candidate?
He had the highest score from
his co-workers during reference checks.
He leads his team
with flexibility and gentle leadership.
Gyu-rim's candidate is known
to be very competent.
But, if I can suggest one more person,
NEXT needs to pull out rotten weeds.
It should be someone who's determined.
I feel much better now.
Shall we get some fresh air?
I want to stay like this for ten minutes.
It's almost over, isn't it?
Yes.
You worked really hard.
You too, Ji-yun.
If the project is successful,
shall we go on a trip?
A trip?
Where?
Anywhere.
Is there somewhere you want to go?
The sea.
I haven't been to the sea in a long time.
The sea sounds great.
Is there anywhere else you want to go?
Tell me. Be it the mountains,
or even outer space.
- Outer space?
- Yes.
Ms. Kang, are you here?
Gyu-rim, what is it?
There you are.
Is Mr. Yu with you?
No, I'm here alone.
He isn't with you?
What? Isn't he at his desk?
No, he isn't. Did he go somewhere?
Maybe he went to the restroom.
That's strange.
I thought I heard his voice here.
People are quite noisy
on the street tonight.
Goodness.
I see.
I'll go.
Work hard, Gyu-rim.
Seriously,
she's so bad at hiding it.
Why did you say that I wasn't here?
I can't tell her
that we were dating at work.
I'll be leaving first.
Come out in five minutes, okay?
What if I get caught?
I'll distract them in the meeting room.
Come out without getting caught.
Okay…
During the last month,
both of you worked very hard
searching for the next CEO at NEXT.
I look forward to seeing what candidates
you will recommend.
Among the candidates you recommend today,
those who pass the application process
will be interviewed.
This is the final list
of candidates from Peoplez.
All of them are CEOs
with legal or journalist backgrounds.
They'd be most efficient in resolving
the crisis for NEXT
in the shortest period of time.
And this is…
APPOINTMENT OF CEO AT NEXT
The risks of those candidates.
We will use this to argue
against Kang Ji-yun's suggestions.
Once the candidates are announced,
with this information,
you can eliminate her candidates
during the application process.
APPOINTMENT OF CEO AT NEXT
PEOPLEZ FINAL LIST OF CANDIDATES
Let's start with Peoplez.
Please tell us about your candidates
and why you recommend them.
Here's the final list of candidates
that we recommend.
All three of them are experts
in human resources.
They're the best CEOs.
While everyone is focusing
on external matters,
they'll bring stability to the company
for the future of NEXT.
I believe
we told you that we needed a CEO
to put our crisis to rest.
Since your former CEO, there has been
division and discrimination
between programmers and nonprogrammers,
managers prioritizing their position
over doing actual work,
and a lack of trust and loyalty
from the employees.
The real crisis at NEXT is…
COMPANY REVIEW ON NEXT
…internal, not external.
I'm sure none of you can deny it.
What eventually changes the company
is its employees.
What leads NEXT
with a sense of responsibility
isn't external assessments.
It's those who currently work at NEXT.
To truly benefit NEXT,
please select carefully
the most appropriate CEO.
The new CEO at the web portal NEXT
has been decided.
Newly appointed CEO Jung Su-hwan stated
bringing stability to the company
as the number one priority.
He added what leads NEXT's future
will be supportive company culture
and employee growth.
"Also, the new CEO at NEXT was appointed
through a search firm called Peoplez!"
Eun-ho!
Good job.
Well done!
Now, we're the exclusive headhunter
for NEXT, right?
The total number of employees
at NEXT is about 4,000.
It's 4,000 people!
Is it just me? I can't believe it.
- You can't believe it?
- No.
I can't believe it either.
What should we do?
We must go out on a company dinner
to believe it!
A company dinner.
Mr. Kim.
He brought it up so naturally.
What's wrong? A company dinner.
A company dinner!
Goodness.
Let's go.
She gave us the corporate card!
- Ms. Kang!
- I made this happen, guys!
- Is everyone in?
- What should we eat?
We can get something big
with the black card.
I'd love some dakgalbi!
Enjoy your food.
It's on us, so enjoy.
Gosh, it looks delicious.
- Come on, Mr. Kim.
- What?
At times like these, you should be QSPN
and move out the way.
QSPN? What's that?
Have you stopped updating your notes?
Am I the only one who doesn't know?
At times like these,
be quick, smart, and polite to notice.
What do you want me to do?
Please get up and change seats.
Mr. Yu, come this way.
- Goodness.
- This way, please.
- Mr. Yu, over here.
- Come this way.
Hurry over here.
- That's good.
- You're being so slow.
And here's my bestie.
They didn't tell us about it,
but I'm still jealous.
- Who wants soju?
- Me!
- Cheers.
- Mr. Kim.
Have you tried this?
It looks delicious.
Why is this so tender?
- Kyung-hwa.
- When it's this tender,
I need a drink.
We should drink at a time like this.
Drinking never felt so easy.
Kwang-hee, let's liven up the mood.
Okay, I'll make us drinks.
Give me your glasses.
- Hand them over.
- Sit back down.
What?
Sit back down.
Sit? Okay.
She must be showing us a new trick.
She's a pro.
What was that about?
I don't like the drinks you make.
You should've told me before.
Gyu-rim, who exactly are you?
All right!
Attention, everyone.
This is a special event to celebrate
the success of our project
and also to promote companionship
among all the employees.
Today…
- One more time!
- Don't do that.
- Drink until the end!
- Stop it.
Oh, please!
Also, Ms. Kang.
To commemorate your joining
the company dinner voluntarily,
- a speech, please.
- A speech? No way.
- I don't want to.
- Come on, Ms. Kang.
- No way. Please.
- Ms. Kang!
Quiet down. As you all know,
this makes her embarrassed.
CEO Kang!
- CEO Kang!
Enough!
Let's work hard again starting tomorrow.
- Gosh.
- I don't think I can.
What's wrong with her?
The project was successful
thanks to all of you.
Thank you.
What's going on?
Enjoy the food tonight.
Let's have fun.
Cheers.
- Cheers!
You grew up well.
Shut up and eat.
Have you thought about
what to do about your job?
Has that been troubling you?
Of course.
It's something that concerns you.
I'd like you to work
where your competence can shine more.
Don't I shine at this company?
I'm starting to feel disappointed.
You know that's not what I mean.
I realized it once again
during our project on NEXT.
It'd be greedy of me to keep
a talented person like you
all to myself.
Wow, you finally acknowledge me, Ms. Kang.
You're getting arrogant already.
Anyway,
don't worry about me.
Make the best decision for yourself.
Okay.
I'll think about it.
It feels warm.
Your hand fits right in.
You just have big hands.
YOU HAVE NEW MESSAGES
Ms. Kang, there are many articles
assuming that it's Peoplez.
Is it true?
IKONIC BIOTECHNOLOGY, FRAUD
OF 20 BILLION WON… CEO VANISHED
Ms. Kang, is it true
that Peoplez was involved?
Were you not aware of it?
Did you recommend the candidate
while knowing?
What will happen to those
hired by the company?
Were you not aware at all?
- I changed jobs because I trusted you.
- What do I do?
- Ms. Kang!
- How could you?
She came here?
- The CEO…
- How dare she show up here?
She's a murderer.
- Don't you know his whereabouts?
- Since when did this happen?
Anything to say to the victims?
Do you have anything to say?
We'll be conducting a search and seizure
of the office.
Why are you lowering the blinds?
Ms. Kang isn't a criminal!
Why are you doing this to me?
Because I hate you.
Career Way will take over Peoplez.
Was it you, Father?
I'm figuring out what to do.
If I expect it to be a loss,
I'd need to make a decision.
Are you okay?
You won't have to worry about Mr. Yu.
I mean, you.
Are you okay, Jeong-hoon?
Ji-yun, you aren't alone.
You weren't and won't be going forth.
I hated my life.
- Good morning.
- You came to work early.
- Ever since I met you,
- Hello!
I started to like myself.
Subtitle translation by: Helena Noh